{
    "id": "3ceb343da1b1452f88b53357e2c586fb",
    "title": "Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She .......................... not have a job.",
            "description": "Have is followed by a past participle do and does are followed by bare infinitives. ",
            "answers": [
                "does",
                "do",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "............................. you heard from them yet?",
            "description": "Have is followed by a past participle do and does are followed by bare infinitives. ",
            "answers": [
                "Did",
                "Do",
                "Have"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We ......................... not throw away anything useful.",
            "description": "Have is followed by a past participle do and does are followed by bare infinitives. ",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "have",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "............................ you know her?",
            "description": "Have is followed by a past participle do and does are followed by bare infinitives. ",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Have",
                "Are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What ............................ you do then?",
            "description": "Then indicates distance in space hence, did is used here. ",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "have",
                "did",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Where ............................. they live?",
            "description": "Have is followed by a past participle do and does are followed by bare infinitives. ",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "have",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Whom ................................ you want to meet?",
            "description": "Have is followed by a past participle do and does are followed by bare infinitives. ",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "do",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How ............................. they escape?",
            "description": "Have is followed by a past participle do, does and did are followed by bare infinitives. ",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "had",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ............................... got a number of friends.",
            "description": "Has indicates possession. ",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "do",
                "have",
                "is"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "............................. they interested in this offer?",
            "description": "Be (is, am, are, was, were) shows state have shows possession. ",
            "answers": [
                "Are",
                "Have",
                "Do"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "........................... I late?",
            "description": "Am indicates state. Have indicates possession.",
            "answers": [
                "Am",
                "Have",
                "Do"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We ........................... no one to help us.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "do",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}